[
  {
    "review": {
      "id": 1,
      "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
      "file_path": "submission1.pdf",
      "done": false
    },
    "form": [
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 5,
          "type_question": "mc",
          "question": "Choose an option2",
          "question_number": 3,
          "option": [
            {
              "id": 13,
              "option": "Option 1 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            },
            {
              "id": 14,
              "option": "Option 2 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            },
            {
              "id": 15,
              "option": "Option 3 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": 15,
          "mcquestion_id": 5,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      },
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Some open question5",
          "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
          "question_number": 1,
          "type_question": "open"
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": "sdsada sadsa sadsada adssdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsasdsada sadsa sadsada adsaa",
          "openquestion_id": 8,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      },
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Give a rating",
          "range": 7,
          "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
          "question_number": 2,
          "type_question": "range"
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": 1,
          "rangequestion_id": 6,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "review": {
      "id": 1,
      "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
      "file_path": "submission1.pdf",
      "done": false
    },
    "form": [
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 5,
          "type_question": "mc",
          "question": "Choose an option2",
          "question_number": 3,
          "option": [
            {
              "id": 13,
              "option": "Option 1 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            },
            {
              "id": 14,
              "option": "Option 2 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            },
            {
              "id": 15,
              "option": "Option 3 (1)",
              "mcquestion_id": 5
            }
          ]
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": 13,
          "mcquestion_id": 5,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      },
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "Some open question5",
          "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
          "question_number": 1,
          "type_question": "open"
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": "sdsada sadsa sd sadsadsasadsada adsa",
          "openquestion_id": 8,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      },
      {
        "question": {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "Give a rating",
          "range": 7,
          "rubric_assignment_id": 4,
          "question_number": 2,
          "type_question": "range"
        },
        "answer": {
          "answer": 5,
          "rangequestion_id": 6,
          "review_id": 1
        }
      }
    ]
  }
]